<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About Hugo</title>
    <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on About Hugo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 22:49:06 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://about-hugo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install Hugo</title>
      <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/install-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/install-hugo/</guid>
      <description>To use this theme you will need to have Hugo installed. If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have Hugo installed please follow the official installation guide&#xA;Check Hugo Version This theme uses Hugo Pipes to compile SCSS and minify assets. Please make sure you have the Hugo Extended version installed. If you are not using the extended version this theme will not not compile.&#xA;hugo version </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Theme</title>
      <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/install-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/install-theme/</guid>
      <description>Create a new Hugo site hugo new site mynewsite This will create a fresh Hugo site in the folder mynewsite.&#xA;Install theme Copy or git clone this theme into the sites themes folder mynewsite/themes&#xA;Install with Git cd mynewsite cd themes git clone https://github.com/jugglerx/hugo-whisper-theme.git Install from .zip file You can download the .zip file located here https://github.com/JugglerX/hugo-whisper-theme/archive/master.zip.&#xA;Extract the downloaded .zip inside the themes folder. Rename the extracted folder from hugo-whisper-theme-master -&amp;gt; hugo-whisper-theme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/configure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:30:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/configure/</guid>
      <description>Syntax highlighting and menus can be configured via &lt;code&gt;config.toml&lt;/code&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specimen</title>
      <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/specimen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/specimen/</guid>
      <description>Markdown Test Page Headings Paragraphs Blockquotes Lists Horizontal rule Table Code Inline elements Headings Heading one Sint sit cillum pariatur eiusmod nulla pariatur ipsum. Sit laborum anim qui mollit tempor pariatur nisi minim dolor. Aliquip et adipisicing sit sit fugiat commodo id sunt. Nostrud enim ad commodo incididunt cupidatat in ullamco ullamco Lorem cupidatat velit enim et Lorem.&#xA;Heading two Aute officia nulla deserunt do deserunt cillum velit magna. Officia veniam culpa anim minim dolore labore pariatur voluptate id ad est duis quis velit dolor pariatur enim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Whisper</title>
      <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://about-hugo.github.io/docs/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whisper is a minimal documentation theme built for Hugo. The design &amp;amp; functionality is intentionally minimal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/hugo/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:10:01 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://about-hugo.github.io/hugo/overview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a web static site generator, hugo takes the site structure and the site content (in markdown format) and&#xA;generates a static web site. The complete web site - HTML, CSS, JS in a directory structure - is then copied to the web server, which only needs to serve these static files.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Creation and Delivery Processes</title>
      <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/hugo/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:44:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://about-hugo.github.io/hugo/process/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most known Web Content Management Systems (like Wordpress, Typo3, Drupal) are Web-Applications&#xA;which integrate content editing and publication in one single application. With a static&#xA;site generator, these process steps are divided: Content creation is done on your&#xA;local computer, and content delivery is done by a static web server like nginx or apache.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing/Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/hugo/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 22:49:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://about-hugo.github.io/hugo/content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content Creation in Hugo is done by editing markdown files.&#xA;The site&amp;rsquo;s structure is defined in templates, which are also plain text files.&#xA;Both  are usually put under version control and edited with the same tools&#xA;used in software development.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment</title>
      <link>https://about-hugo.github.io/hugo/deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 21:13:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://about-hugo.github.io/hugo/deployment/</guid>
      <description>As for the content creation, software engineering tools are used for deployment.&#xA;This page showcases automated deployment using github actions. On the various example sites and theme tryouts, explore the Actions tab in github and the workflow definitions located in .github/workflows.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
